[
    {
        "qid": 214108,
        "question": "Patient is a 24 year old male.<br>- The patient has pain somewhere, related to their reason for consulting.<br>- The patient's pain is haunting, a knife stroke, tugging, burning, sickening, and scary.<br>- The patient feels pain in the right hypochondrium and epigastric regions.<br>- The patient's pain intensity is 4 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain does not radiate to another location.<br>- The pain is located with a precision of 6 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain appeared at a speed of 1 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient drinks alcohol excessively or has an addiction to alcohol.<br>- The patient has a hiatal hernia.<br>- The patient has asthma or has had to use a bronchodilator in the past.<br>- The patient has a burning sensation that starts in their stomach, goes up into their throat, and can be associated with a bitter taste in their mouth.<br>- The patient has not traveled out of the country in the last 4 weeks.<br>- The patient has symptoms that get worse after eating.",
        "option1": "Gastroesophageal reflux disease (GERD)",
        "option2": "Pancreatic neoplasm",
        "option3": "Unstable angina",
        "option4": "Possible NSTEMI / STEMI",
        "correct_option": 1,
        "ai_prediction": 2,
        "ai_confidence": "63%",
        "ai_is_correct": false
    },
    {
        "qid": 988195,
        "question": "Patient is a 3 year old female.<br>- The patient has recently had a viral infection.<br>- The patient has pain somewhere, related to their reason for consulting.<br>- The patient's pain is sensitive, like a knife stroke.<br>- The patient feels pain in the lower chest, the right side of the chest, and the right breast.<br>- The intensity of the patient's pain is 3 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain does not radiate to another location.<br>- The patient's pain is precisely located at a level of 1 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain appeared at a speed of 0 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient feels out of breath with minimal physical effort.<br>- The patient is experiencing shortness of breath or difficulty breathing in a significant way.<br>- The patient feels their heart is beating fast (racing), irregularly (missing a beat), or they feel palpitations.<br>- The patient has not traveled out of the country in the last 4 weeks.<br>- The patient's symptoms are worse when lying down and alleviated while sitting up.",
        "option1": "Gastroesophageal reflux disease (GERD)",
        "option2": "Chagas",
        "option3": "Myocarditis",
        "option4": "Sarcoidosis",
        "correct_option": 3,
        "ai_prediction": 3,
        "ai_confidence": "76%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": 913182,
        "question": "Patient is a 13 year old female.<br>- The patient has recently had a viral infection.<br>- The patient has pain somewhere, related to their reason for consulting.<br>- The patient's pain is sensitive.<br>- The patient feels pain on the right side of the chest.<br>- The patient's pain is at an intensity of 6 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain does not radiate to another location.<br>- The pain is located with a precision of 6 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain appeared at a speed of 0 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient feels out of breath with minimal physical effort.<br>- The patient is experiencing shortness of breath or difficulty breathing in a significant way.<br>- The patient has not traveled out of the country in the last 4 weeks.<br>- The patient's symptoms are worse when lying down and alleviated while sitting up.",
        "option1": "Scombroid food poisoning",
        "option2": "Pulmonary embolism",
        "option3": "Sarcoidosis",
        "option4": "Myocarditis",
        "correct_option": 4,
        "ai_prediction": 4,
        "ai_confidence": "48%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": 90600,
        "question": "Patient is a 41 year old male.<br>- The patient has a poor diet.<br>- The patient has had a diagnosis of anemia.<br>- The patient has family members who have been diagnosed with anemia.<br>- The patient has pain somewhere, related to their reason for consulting.<br>- The patient's pain is characterized as a cramp.<br>- The patient feels pain in the right temple and left temple.<br>- The intensity of the patient's pain is 2 on a scale of 0 to 10.<br>- The patient's pain does not radiate to another location.<br>- The pain is precisely located at a level of 6 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain appeared at a speed of 1 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient feels slightly dizzy or lightheaded.<br>- The patient feels lightheaded and dizzy or feels like they are about to faint.<br>- The patient feels so tired that they are unable to do their usual activities or are stuck in bed all day long.<br>- The patient has chronic kidney failure.<br>- The patient has recently had stools that were black, like coal.<br>- The patient is taking new oral anticoagulants (NOACs).<br>- The patient's skin is much paler than usual.<br>- The patient has noticed light red blood or blood clots in their stool.<br>- The patient has traveled to Asia in the last 4 weeks.<br>- The patient's BMI is less than 18.5, indicating they are underweight.",
        "option1": "Paroxysmal supraventricular tachycardia (PSVT)",
        "option2": "Atrial fibrillation",
        "option3": "Cluster headache",
        "option4": "Anemia",
        "correct_option": 4,
        "ai_prediction": 4,
        "ai_confidence": "66%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": 177632,
        "question": "Patient is a 59 year old male.<br>- The patient has pain somewhere, related to their reason for consulting.<br>- The patient's pain is haunting, sensitive, and sickening.<br>- The patient feels pain in the upper chest, hypochondrium (left), and epigastric regions.<br>- The intensity of the patient's pain is 6 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain radiates to the lower chest.<br>- The pain is precisely located at a level of 6 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain appeared at a speed of 0 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient is significantly overweight compared to people of the same height.<br>- The patient has a hiatal hernia.<br>- The patient has a burning sensation that starts in their stomach, goes up into their throat, and can be associated with a bitter taste in their mouth.<br>- The patient has not traveled out of the country in the last 4 weeks.<br>- The patient has symptoms that get worse after eating.",
        "option1": "Unstable angina",
        "option2": "Pancreatic neoplasm",
        "option3": "Possible NSTEMI / STEMI",
        "option4": "Gastroesophageal reflux disease (GERD)",
        "correct_option": 4,
        "ai_prediction": 4,
        "ai_confidence": "95%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": 681664,
        "question": "Patient is a 17 year old male.<br>- The patient has pain somewhere, related to their reason for consulting.<br>- The patient's pain is sensitive.<br>- The patient feels pain in the right breast, left breast, and right posterior chest wall.<br>- The intensity of the patient's pain is 4 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain does not radiate to another location.<br>- The pain is precisely located at a level of 3 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain appeared at a speed of 0 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient has a sore throat.<br>- The patient has chronic obstructive pulmonary disease (COPD).<br>- The patient has a cough.<br>- The patient has not traveled out of the country in the last 4 weeks.<br>- The patient has noticed a wheezing sound when they exhale.",
        "option1": "Upper respiratory tract infection (URTI)",
        "option2": "Bronchitis",
        "option3": "Anaphylaxis",
        "option4": "Scombroid food poisoning",
        "correct_option": 2,
        "ai_prediction": 2,
        "ai_confidence": "92%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": 532269,
        "question": "Patient is a 26 year old male.<br>- The patient has felt confused or disorientated lately.<br>- The patient has been in contact with a person with similar symptoms in the past 2 weeks.<br>- The patient has had diarrhea or an increase in stool frequency.<br>- The patient has been in contact with someone infected with the Ebola virus in the last month.<br>- The patient constantly feels fatigued or has non-restful sleep.<br>- The patient has diffuse (widespread) muscle pain.<br>- The patient has noticed unusual bleeding or bruising related to their consultation today.<br>- The patient has a cough.<br>- The patient has traveled to West Africa in the last 4 weeks.",
        "option1": "Anemia",
        "option2": "Pancreatic neoplasm",
        "option3": "Bronchitis",
        "option4": "Ebola",
        "correct_option": 4,
        "ai_prediction": 4,
        "ai_confidence": "64%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": 82633,
        "question": "Patient is a 0 year old female.<br>- The patient has recently had a viral infection.<br>- The patient has pain somewhere, related to their reason for consulting.<br>- The patient's pain is sensitive.<br>- The patient feels pain on the right side of the chest, the left side of the chest, and the right breast.<br>- The intensity of the patient's pain is 4 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain does not radiate to another location.<br>- The pain is precisely located at a level of 7 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain appeared at a speed of 1 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient feels out of breath with minimal physical effort.<br>- The patient is experiencing shortness of breath or difficulty breathing in a significant way.<br>- The patient has not traveled out of the country in the last 4 weeks.<br>- The patient has symptoms that are increased with physical exertion but alleviated with rest.",
        "option1": "Myocarditis",
        "option2": "Systemic lupus erythematosus (SLE)",
        "option3": "Chagas",
        "option4": "Scombroid food poisoning",
        "correct_option": 1,
        "ai_prediction": 2,
        "ai_confidence": "53%",
        "ai_is_correct": false
    },
    {
        "qid": 78836,
        "question": "Patient is a 1 year old male.<br>- The patient has pain somewhere, related to their reason for consulting.<br>- The patient's pain is characterized as burning.<br>- The patient feels pain in the lower chest, the right side of the chest, and the left posterior chest wall.<br>- The intensity of the patient's pain is 4 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain does not radiate to another location.<br>- The pain is precisely located at a level of 2 (on a scale of 0 to 10) for the patient.<br>- The patient's pain appeared at a speed of 5 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient has a sore throat.<br>- The patient has a cough.<br>- The patient has not traveled out of the country in the last 4 weeks.<br>- The patient's vaccinations are up to date.<br>- The patient's symptoms are more prominent at night.",
        "option1": "Bronchitis",
        "option2": "Gastroesophageal reflux disease (GERD)",
        "option3": "Pneumonia",
        "option4": "Upper respiratory tract infection (URTI)",
        "correct_option": 1,
        "ai_prediction": 1,
        "ai_confidence": "88%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": 332679,
        "question": "Patient is a 0 year old female.<br>- The patient has pain somewhere, related to their reason for consulting.<br>- The patient's pain is sensitive and burning.<br>- The patient feels pain on the right side of the chest, left side of the chest, upper chest, and right posterior chest wall.<br>- The intensity of the patient's pain is 4 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain does not radiate to another location.<br>- The pain is precisely located at a level of 6 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain appeared at a speed of 0 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient smokes cigarettes.<br>- The patient has a sore throat.<br>- The patient has chronic obstructive pulmonary disease (COPD).<br>- The patient has a cough.<br>- The patient has not traveled out of the country in the last 4 weeks.<br>- The patient's symptoms are more prominent at night.",
        "option1": "Gastroesophageal reflux disease (GERD)",
        "option2": "Bronchitis",
        "option3": "Pneumonia",
        "option4": "Upper respiratory tract infection (URTI)",
        "correct_option": 2,
        "ai_prediction": 2,
        "ai_confidence": "59%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": 1085494,
        "question": "Patient is a 1 year old male.<br>- The patient has been in contact with a person with similar symptoms in the past 2 weeks.<br>- The patient lives with 4 or more people.<br>- The patient has pain somewhere, related to their reason for consulting.<br>- The patient's pain is sensitive.<br>- The patient feels pain at the top of the head, forehead, right cheek, left cheek, and left temple.<br>- The intensity of the patient's pain is 2 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain does not radiate to another location.<br>- The pain is precisely located at a level of 7 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain appeared at a speed of 3 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient smokes cigarettes.<br>- The patient has a sore throat.<br>- The patient has nasal congestion or a clear runny nose.<br>- The patient has not traveled out of the country in the last 4 weeks.",
        "option1": "Anemia",
        "option2": "Chagas",
        "option3": "Acute otitis media",
        "option4": "Upper respiratory tract infection (URTI)",
        "correct_option": 4,
        "ai_prediction": 4,
        "ai_confidence": "92%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": 276243,
        "question": "Patient is a 7 year old male.<br>- The patient has felt confused or disorientated lately.<br>- The patient has been in contact with a person with similar symptoms in the past 2 weeks.<br>- The patient has had diarrhea or an increase in stool frequency.<br>- The patient has been in contact with someone infected with the Ebola virus in the last month.<br>- The patient constantly feels fatigued or has non-restful sleep.<br>- The patient has a fever, either felt or measured with a thermometer.<br>- The patient is feeling nauseous or feels like vomiting.<br>- The patient has noticed unusual bleeding or bruising related to their consultation today.<br>- The patient has a cough.<br>- The patient has traveled to West Africa in the last 4 weeks.",
        "option1": "HIV (initial infection)",
        "option2": "Ebola",
        "option3": "Bronchitis",
        "option4": "Pneumonia",
        "correct_option": 2,
        "ai_prediction": 4,
        "ai_confidence": "75%",
        "ai_is_correct": false
    },
    {
        "qid": 856081,
        "question": "Patient is a 5 year old male.<br>- The patient lives with 4 or more people.<br>- The patient attends or works in a daycare.<br>- The patient has pain somewhere, related to their reason for consulting.<br>- The patient's pain is sensitive.<br>- The patient feels pain in the right tonsil, left tonsil, thyroid cartilage, pharynx, and under the jaw.<br>- The intensity of the patient's pain is 4 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain does not radiate to another location.<br>- The patient's pain is precisely located at a level of 7 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain appeared at a speed of 3 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient smokes cigarettes.<br>- The patient has a fever, either felt or measured with a thermometer.<br>- The patient has had a cold in the last 2 weeks.<br>- The patient has traveled to North America in the last 4 weeks.<br>- The patient has noticed that the tone of their voice has become deeper, softer, or hoarse.",
        "option1": "Acute laryngitis",
        "option2": "Viral pharyngitis",
        "option3": "Chagas",
        "option4": "Epiglottitis",
        "correct_option": 1,
        "ai_prediction": 1,
        "ai_confidence": "66%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": 448598,
        "question": "Patient is a 54 year old male.<br>- The patient has had diarrhea or an increase in stool frequency.<br>- The patient has been in contact with someone infected with the Ebola virus in the last month.<br>- The patient constantly feels fatigued or has non-restful sleep.<br>- The patient has a sore throat.<br>- The patient has noticed unusual bleeding or bruising related to their consultation today.<br>- The patient has a cough.<br>- The patient has traveled to West Africa in the last 4 weeks.",
        "option1": "Bronchitis",
        "option2": "Anemia",
        "option3": "Ebola",
        "option4": "Pancreatic neoplasm",
        "correct_option": 3,
        "ai_prediction": 3,
        "ai_confidence": "46%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": 1031914,
        "question": "Patient is a 8 year old male.<br>- The patient attends or works in a daycare.<br>- The patient has pain somewhere, related to their reason for consulting.<br>- The patient's pain is sensitive.<br>- The patient feels pain in the left tonsil, palate, pharynx, under the jaw, and trachea.<br>- The patient's pain intensity is 1 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain does not radiate to another location.<br>- The patient's pain is precisely located at a level of 2 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain appeared at a speed of 4 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient smokes cigarettes.<br>- The patient has a fever, either felt or measured with a thermometer.<br>- The patient has had a cold in the last 2 weeks.<br>- The patient has traveled to North America in the last 4 weeks.<br>- The patient has noticed that the tone of their voice has become deeper, softer, or hoarse.",
        "option1": "Chagas",
        "option2": "Viral pharyngitis",
        "option3": "Acute laryngitis",
        "option4": "Epiglottitis",
        "correct_option": 3,
        "ai_prediction": 3,
        "ai_confidence": "58%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    }
]